= kisskh.asia =
Honey, help me!
Lin Zai!
Brother!
Help me!
Lin Zai!
It's too late!
This way!
Hurry!
Go!
Hurry up, Lin Zai!
This way!
Over here!
Move!
Brother, it won't open!
Brother!
The door's open! Hurry!
Kid.
It's not safe for us here anymore.
We need to hurry
and find a new way out.
I just
saw the floor plan in the hallway.
I remember where the exit is.
Brother.
Don't worry.
I'll definitely get you out of here.
If my little brother says so,
then it's a sure thing.
Let's go.
Lin Zai!
Brother!
Get out of here!
You have to survive.
Go!
Leave me!
Brother!
You
must
live.
My name is Lin Zai.
Twenty-two days ago,
the zombie outbreak suddenly hit,
destroying my life
and taking away my family.
Just now,
I lost my brother too.
And now,
I've been bitten as well.
It's all over.
They say
you only have a few hours
of sanity left after being bitten.
I didn't know it would hurt this much.
That it would be this cold.
I'll slowly forget who I am.
I guess.
I'm on my way there.
Honey, are you okay?
I'm fine.
Your lips are pale.
Why are you sweating so much?
I'm fine.
Please!
Please don't kill me!
Please don't kill him!
Please!
Honey!
No immune subjects found.
Keep searching.
I didn't turn into a zombie.
[TN: The character for "praying"]
You have to survive.
Brother,
I promise I will survive.
Even if it's just for one more day.
"The Last Oath"
(Episode 1: Infection)
(Six months later)
Lin Zai, come here for a sec!
Coming!
What's up, Brother Li?
I changed the bulb, but
it's still not turning on.
Let me take a look.
You need to fix it quick.
Zombies got in last night.
What?
Don't panic.
Sister Chen took care of it.
Sister Chen is the best.
Here, hand it to me.
Careful now.
Here, try it.
Awesome.
Let's go.
Let's go grab some food.
Okay.
College kids really know their stuff.
All I can do is change a bulb
or fix a faucet.
For delicate work like this,
we have to rely on you.
Brother Li,
Yeah?
you're the one with super strength.
You carried me up five flights
of stairs without breaking a sweat.
When it counts,
you're way more useful than I am.
Listen here, you brat.
Are you indirectly calling me
all brawn and no brains?
No, no, not at all.
Next time we haul supplies,
you're carrying double the load.
Otherwise, don't bother coming back.
And no dinner for you.
I was just about to go in and get you two.
Time to eat!
Grandma Qiu, let me help.
Oh, my.
People need to eat.
You need a full stomach
to have the energy to work.
Today,
we have the sparrow
meat you've been craving.
Hold your horses. We'll eat
when Xiao Chen gets here.
Where is Xiao Chen?
Xiao Chen?
She should be in the backyard.
I'll go get her.
Okay.
Sister Chen, food's ready!
Good thing you suggested
adding more defenses yesterday.
Otherwise, we would've
been toast last night.
As long as it works.
But we still can't let our guard down.
Oh, come on.
It's fine.
Don't worry.
Our camp is well hidden.
A few stray zombies now and then?
I can handle them with my eyes closed.
You're a badass, Sister Chen.
I'm going to double-check the other traps.
You go ahead and eat.
Alright, be careful.
Brother.
You must be watching over me
from heaven, keeping me from turning.
Until my time comes,
I promise I'll survive.
Go!
Leave me!
Don't touch him!
What are you doing?
What if he's a zombie?
Looks like he's not infected.
These are just fall and scrape wounds.
Looks like he fell from somewhere.
Probably has some internal
injuries and fractures too.
To make it all the way to our camp,
he must have run into
a lot of zombies along the way.
Can he be saved?
Hard to say.
But we'd better stay out of this.
We're already low on supplies.
And looking at his gear,
he might even be a looter.
We have to prioritize the camp's safety.
Buddy,
I'm sorry.
We'd love to help,
but our hands are tied.
Sorry about this.
Whoa.
Bandages,
a huge coil of climbing rope,
and a small flashlight.
This guy's no joke.
Food,
tools.
Everything our camp needs.
Aside from looters,
I doubt anyone would
carry such a complete set of gear
while wandering around out here.
It is pretty comprehensive.
But in times like these,
it's better to be safe than sorry.
After all, this camp of ours
took a lot of effort
to build from the ground up.
Yeah.
You have a point.
No matter the era,
humanity's greatest enemy is always itself.
Humanity's greatest enemy is always itself.
All right, all right.
Stop dwelling on it.
Even in peacetime,
if someone just collapsed on the street,
people would hesitate to help.
Let alone nowadays.
Captain Chen made the right call.
And you weren't wrong for wanting to help.
I know.
I just...
Never mind.
Let's drop it.
What goodies did you find?
Let me see.
Hey.
This is for kids.
It's a bit too childish.
It's perfect for someone like you,
a young college guy.
A gift from your big bro.
Even a college guy finds it childish.
Then...
Hey.
How about this?
This one's stylish.
Thanks, Brother Li.
When I get the game console fixed,
I'll let you have the first go.
That's more like it.
You'd better not be a Marauder.
Otherwise, my good deed will backfire.
Hey.
How are you holding up?
Hang in there.
Hey.
Wake up.
Hey!
Don't die on me.
I went through hell to carry you back here.
Don't let all my effort go to waste.
Hey.
Wake up.